A Guide to the Great Falls Historical Society, Virginia Collection, c.1960s-2022
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
The Great Falls Historical Society, Virginia Collection, c.1960s-2022
Fairfax County Public Library
MSS 05-75
18.5 linear feet
The Great Falls Historical Society, Virginia Collection spans the years c.1960s-2022 and consists of photographs, negatives, slides, general subject files, newsletters, publications, financial records, original research, oral histories, and other materials maintained by the Society during its existence from 1977-2021.
Great Falls Historical Society, Virginia
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None
Acquisition Information
Artwork in this collection was donated by the Great Falls Historical Society in September 2019. Douglas Cobb, Vice-President and Treasurer, donated the Society’s records in February 2021.
Historical and Biographical Information
In February 1977, five residents of Great Falls, Virginia got together and held the first meeting of the Great Falls Historical Society (GFHS). Two of those residents, Milburn Sanders and Anthony Holland, had previously discussed organizing a historical society to record and preserve the history of the Great Falls area. At their meeting on April 26, 1977, the group adopted by-laws and officially assumed the name “The Great Falls Historical Society, Virginia”. The original officers were: Milburn Sanders, president; Ray McClure, vice president; Jeannette Bryant, secretary; Richard Kerr, treasurer; William Jackson, board member; Marion Reid, board member; and Karen Creuziger, board member.
For over 40 years, the Society held monthly programs on local history, advocated for the preservation and protection of historic structures in Great Falls, conducted oral histories with long-time residents, offered tours of historic sites, published books and a newsletter, and collected and preserved historical artifacts and photographs of the area. The Society, a non-profit 501(c)3, also hosted events such as an annual Great Falls Day, and Grange and Old School Days. Membership was open to everyone and most meetings occurred either in the Great Falls Grange Hall or Great Falls Library Meeting Room.
In 2021, after more than 40 years of promoting and documenting Great Falls’ history, the Society reached the difficult decision to dissolve. In its last years, the Society struggled with declining membership, program attendance, and a lack of interest from volunteers to take on leadership roles. They transferred their collection of photographs and organizational records to Fairfax County Public Library’s Virginia Room in February 2021.
Scope and Content
The Great Falls Historical Society, Virginia Collection spans the years c.1960s-2022 and consists of photographs, negatives, slides, general subject files, newsletters, publications, financial records, original research, oral histories, and other materials maintained by the Society during its existence from 1977-2021. Subjects covered are the activities of the Society and history of Great Falls, Virginia.
Series 1: General Subject Files, 1977-2021, Boxes 1-3
This series contains general subject files and documents maintained by the GFHS. Included are the Society’s by-laws and constitution, rosters, meeting minutes, lists, newspaper articles, resolutions, website printouts, reports, stationary, a plaque, and a ticket from the defunct Great Falls Park Carousel.
Series 2: Events, 1977-2019, Box 3
This series contains documents relating to events hosted by the GFHS. Events included are Grange and Old School Days, Great Falls Day, and the GFHS 40th Anniversary Gala Celebration. Also included are a list of programs that the Society hosted from 1977-2019.
Series 3: Newsletters, 1980-2018, Boxes 4-5
This series contains the GFHS-produced newsletters. The Society initially put out an untitled monthly newsletter that featured meeting announcements from 1980-1981. The newsletter went through subsequent name changes beginning with “Great Falls Courier” in March 1982, “The Courier” in May 1982, “Postilion” in September 1982, and finally “Chronicler” in September 1982. “Chronicler” remained the Society’s newsletter name until it dissolved in 2021. The last issue appears to have been published in September 2018. The newsletter reported on the Society’s activities, upcoming programs, and other news relating to Great Falls history.
Series 4: Publications, 1982-2007, Boxes 6 and 31
This series contains a selection of publications produced by the GFHS. Included are annual reports, brochures, calendars, and an artboard for their 1987 cookbook "How To Cure A Thousand Pounds Of Ham And Other Receipts".
Series 5: Financial Records, 1981-2022, Box 7
This series contains financial records maintained by the GFHS. Included are budgets, checks and check carbons, financial statements, membership lists, tax documents, treasurer’s reports, and other financial paperwork for GFHS-sponsored events.
Series 6: Colvin Run Historic District Proposal, 1997-2018, Boxes 8-13
This series contains materials from the GFHS' efforts to get the Colvin Run Historic District listed on the National Register of Historic Places. Tanya Beauchamp initially submitted an application to the Virginia Department of Historic Resources (VDHR) to do so in 2005. Beginning in 2012, the Society began researching and assembling a final nomination, but VDHR ultimately rejected it in 2018. Included here is the final nomination, drafts, correspondence, reports, and research documentation.
Series 7: Oral Histories, 1978-2012, Boxes 14-18
On January 22, 1980, the GFHS voted to buy a recorder to record oral histories and programs of the Society’s meetings. This series contains oral histories with longtime Great Falls residents that the GFHS conducted and collected. They are featured on cassette tapes, CD-ROMs, DVDs, floppy disks, and as written transcripts. This series is arranged alphabetically by surname. Additional transcriptions of oral histories conducted by the GFHS not featured in this collection can be found on the reference shelves in the Virginia Room’s catalog.
Series 8: Photographic Materials, c. 1960s-2001, Boxes 19-30
Sub-series 8-1: Slides, 1978-1997, Box 19
This series contains photographic slides, both color and black & white, that feature Great Falls houses, barns, businesses, schools, farms, and residents. Many of these slides exist as photographs in Sub-series 8-3 and 8-4.
Sub-series 8-2: Negatives, c.1960s-2001, Boxes 19-20
This series contains negatives including 4x5 sheet film; 35mm negative film; and 120 negative film. Images feature Great Falls people, houses, businesses, historic sites, and GFHS events. Box 20 contains negatives that were not labeled by the GFHS and remain unidentified.
Sub-series 8-3: Photo Albums, 1979-2001, Boxes 21-23 and 30
This series contains photo albums assembled by the GFHS. Photographs depict Great Falls people, historic sites, and GFHS events. Almost every photo was labeled on the back with a unique accession number, however a corresponding index was not included with this collection. Most of the photographs have been identified. The albums have been retained in their original order.
Sub-series 8-4: Photographs, 1979-1993, Boxes 24-27
This series contains loose photographs that were not included in the photo albums but are labeled with the same unique accession numbering system. These photos were mounted onto colored cardstock. Subjects include Great Falls people, places, and historic sites. The photographs are arranged alphabetically by their accession number.
Sub-series 8-5: Oversize Photographs, 1977-1980, Boxes 28-30
This series contains oversize photographs that were too large to contain in Sub-series 8-4. Each photo was labeled by the GFHS with a unique accession number. Subjects include Great Falls people, places, and historic sites. The oversize photographs are arranged alphabetically by their accession number.
Sub-series 8-6: Digital Photos, 2005-2015, Box 27
This series contains digital photos featured on CD-ROMs and DVDs. Included are images of historic Great Falls houses, structures, the dedication of the Great Falls fire station, and scans of some of the photographs found within this collection.
Series 9: Artwork, 2010, undated, Oversize Drawer
This series contains artwork collected by the GFHS. Included are watercolor prints by Susanne Riva, a framed charcoal sketch of a red barn in Great Falls, and two signs: one homemade sign for the Old Georgetown Pike Toll Gate and another that came from Thelma’s Country Store formerly located on Colvin Run Road.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
None
Insignificant financial records including invoices, receipts, tax forms, and bank statements were destroyed.
Index Terms
Great Falls (Va.) - History; Great Falls Historical Society, Virginia
Container List
- Series 1: General Subject Files, 1977-2021
  - By-laws and Constitution, 1993-2016
  - Colvin Run Miller's House Restoration, 2004
  - Committee Roster, 2018
  - Georgetown Pike, 2007-2012
  - Georgetown Pike - Nomination to the National Register of Historic Places, 2012
  - GFHS Inventory of Collections, 2017
  - GFHS Logo, Undated
  - GFHS Stationary, Undated
  - Great Falls 2020 Vision Survey, 2007
  - Great Falls Grange and School House - Park Authority, 2016
  - Great Falls Grange Historic Structure Report, 2008
  - Great Falls Grange Research, 2003-2014
  - Great Falls Park Carousel (ticket), Undated
  - "Great Falls, Virginia Historical Highlights" (1969) by Clare Hudson, Undated
  - History of the GFHS, Undated
  - Home and Community Club of Great Falls, Virginia, Undated
  - Intellectual Property Protection, 2017
  - List of GFHS Officers and Directors, 2003-2020
  - List of Longtime Great Falls Residents, Undated
  - List of Past GFHS Presidents 1977-2017, 2017
  - Minutes - Board Meetings, 1989-1994
  - Minutes - Board Meetings, 2011, 2013
  - Minutes - Board Meetings, 2016-2017
  - Minutes - Board Meetings, 2017-2018
  - Minutes - General Meetings, 1990-1994
  - Newspaper articles, 1982-2018
  - Newspaper articles - album pages (1 of 2), 1993-2013
  - Newspaper articles - album pages (2 of 2), 1977-2003
  - President's Reports, 1988-1990
  - Program Ideas, 2017-2018
  - Resolutions, 2011, 2017
  - Road Histories, Undated
  - Smith Chapel UMC Community Service Award to GFHS (plaque), 1999 May 16
  - Tibbets Award Winners, 2017
  - Turner Farmhouse, 2011-2013
  - Website, 2021
- Series 2: Events, 1977-2019
  - List of Programs, 1977-2019
  - Old School Day, 1996
  - Grange and Old School Days, 1998
  - Grange and Old School Days, 1999
  - Great Falls Heritage Days, 2000
  - Great Falls Day, 2001
  - Great Falls Day, 2002
  - Great Falls Day, 2006
  - Great Falls Day, 2013
  - Great Falls Day, 2014
  - 40th Anniversary Gala Celebration, 2017
- Series 3: Newsletters, 1980-2018
  - Meeting Announcements, 1980-1982, 1990
  - The Courier / Postillion, 1982
  - Chronicler, 1982
  - Chronicler, 1983
  - Chronicler, 1984
  - Chronicler, 1985
  - Chronicler, 1986
  - Chronicler, 1987
  - Chronicler, 1988
  - Chronicler, 1989
  - Chronicler, 1990
  - Chronicler, 1991
  - Chronicler, 1992
  - Chronicler, 1993
  - Chronicler, 1994
  - Chronicler, 1995
  - Chronicler, 1996
  - Chronicler, 1997
  - Chronicler, 1998
  - Chronicler, 1999
  - Chronicler, 2000
  - Chronicler, 2001
  - Chronicler, 2002
  - Chronicler, 2003
  - Chronicler, 2004
  - Chronicler, 2005
  - Chronicler, 2006
  - Chronicler, 2007
  - Chronicler, 2008
  - Chronicler, 2009
  - Chronicler, 2010
  - Chronicler, 2011
  - Chronicler, 2012
  - Chronicler, 2013
  - Chronicler, 2016
  - Chronicler, 2017
  - Chronicler, 2018
- Series 4: Publications, 1982-2007
  - Annual Report / Reflections, 1982-1985
  - Annual Report / Reflections, 1985-1986
  - Annual Report / Reflections, 1986-1988
  - Annual Report / Reflections, 1988-1994
  - Annual Report / Reflections, 1994-1996
  - Annual Report / Reflections, 2007
  - Brochures, "Great Falls Historical Society", 1992-1995
  - Brochure, "Great Falls Historical Society", Undated
  - GFHS Calendar, 1991
  - GFHS Calendar, 1997
  - GFHS Calendar, 1999
  - GFHS Calendar, 2000
  - GFHS Calendar, 2006
  - GFHS Publications Inventory, 2020
  - Artboards for GFHS Cookbook "How To Cure A Thousand Pounds Of Ham And Other Receipts", 1987
- Series 5: Financial Records, 1981-2022
  - Budgets, 1984-1994, 2014-2019
  - Business Membership Applications, 2017
  - Check Carbons, 2009-2012
  - Check Carbons, 2012-2016
  - Check Carbons, 2016-2017
  - Check Examples, 2005
  - Closing Financial Documents, 2016-2022
  - Donations, 2017-2018
  - Executive Transaction Register, 2018-2021
  - Financial Statements, 2011, 2014-2019
  - GFHS 1984 Festival, 1984
  - Great Falls Day 2001, 2001
  - Great Falls Day 2002, 2002
  - Jean Tibbetts Memorial, 2004
  - Membership Lists, 1989-1993
  - Membership Lists, 1994-1997
  - Membership Lists, 2017-2018
  - Permanent Home and Archiving Project, 2015
  - Tax Information, 1981-2016
  - Treasurers Reports, 1989-1995, 2004-2005
  - USPS Bulk Permit, 1990-2005
- Series 6: Colvin Run Historic District Proposal, 1997-2018
  - "Colvin Run, A Historic District?" - GFHS Summer 2012 Intern Research Project, 2012
  - Colvin Run Historic District Nomination (draft), 2017
  - Colvin Run Historic District Nomination (draft with notes), 2017
  - Colvin Run Historic District Nomination (final with CD-ROMs), 2018
  - Colvin Run Historic District Nomination - Appeal Documentation, 2018
  - Colvin Run Historic District Nomination - Archaeological Reports, 1997-2013
  - Colvin Run Historic District Nomination - Correspondence, 2013, 2018
  - Colvin Run Historic District Nomination - PIF Documentation, 2012-2013
  - Colvin Run Historic District Nomination - Preliminary Research, 2012
  - Colvin Run Historic District Nomination - Project Information, 2016-2017
  - Colvin Run Historic District Nomination - Property Owners [CD-ROM], 2017
  - Colvin Run Road - PIF Documentation, 2000-2005
  - Research - Cockrill Family - 1883-1900 Tax Records, Undated
  - Research - Cockrill Family - Chancery No. 6387, Undated
  - Research - Colvin Run Historic District Narrative, 2017
  - Research - Colvin Run Mill (1 of 9), 2017
  - Research - Colvin Run Mill (2 of 9), 2017
  - Research - Colvin Run Mill (3 of 9), 2017
  - Research - Colvin Run Mill (4 of 9), 2017
  - Research - Colvin Run Mill (5 of 9), 2017
  - Research - Colvin Run Mill (6 of 9), 2017
  - Research - Colvin Run Mill (7 of 9), 2017
  - Research - Colvin Run Mill (8 of 9), 2017
  - Research - Colvin Run Mill (9 of 9), 2017
  - Research - Colvin Run Mill - Miller's House, Barn, Cockrill Store, 2013-2017
  - Research - Colvin Run Road - P.I.F. Addendum, 2012-2013
  - Research - Colvin Run Road & Difficult Run Bridge, 2017
  - Research - Colvin Run Schoolhouse, 10201 Colvin Run Road, 2017
  - Research - Difficult Run Bridge Ruins, 2017
  - Research - Fitzgerald's Store, 1139 Walker Road, 2017
  - Research - The Leigh House, 1148 Walker Road, 2017
  - Research - The Leigh House - Additional Research, 2017
  - Research - M. Cockrill General Store, 10014 Colvin Run Road, 2013-2018
  - Research - Mark Cockrill Farmstead, 10020 Colvin Run Road, 2013-2017
  - Research - Matteer House, 10208 Colvin Run Road, 2013-2018
  - Research - Money House, 10014 Colvin Run Road (Parcel 22A and 22), 2017
  - Research - National Register Final Documents, 2017
  - Research - Oliver House, 10101 Colvin Run Road, 2007-2011
  - Research - Stonewall Cockrill Blacksmith House, 10010 Colvin Run Road, 2013-2017
- Series 7: Oral Histories, 1978-2012
  - Arnon Chapel House Tour [DVD], 2012 April 23
  - Warren Beach, 1983?
  - Burdick Brittin, Undated
  - Paul Cornwell [2 tapes], 1984 March
  - Mrs. Otrich Sharper Costley, 1985 April 10
  - Otrich Sharper Costley, 1991 April 22
  - Myrtle Crippen [2 tapes], 1991 March 25
  - Dairy Farming - Beanie Lambert and Rick Oliver [DVD], 2012 March 28
  - James Donn & Joseph Ellis [3 tapes], 1984 March 2
  - James Elgin [transcript and floppy disk], 1983
  - Joseph Ellis, 1984 May 17
  - Joseph Ellis, 1984 June 21
  - Robert Fitzgerald [3 tapes], 1984 October 24
  - Walton Follin [2 tapes], 1994 October 9
  - Ruth Garver [DVD], 2012 April 16
  - Manning Gasch, 1978
  - Martha Getchell, 1984 February
  - Kathry Follin Greene, 1984?
  - Richard Hammond [2 tapes], 1984 February 24
  - Margaret Hopkins, Undated
  - Connie Turner Janssen, Undated
  - Bessie W. Jenkins, 1982 May 28
  - Johnson House Tour [DVD], 2012 April 23
  - Herman Kepart [4 tapes], 1986 April 16
  - Jean Lee [DVD], 2012 March 12
  - Bob Lundegard [DVD], 2012 April 9
  - James Maglione [floppy disk], 1994
  - Ellen Maurice, 1987 March 3
  - Virginia McGavin, 1984 April 12
  - Carolyn Cornwell Miller [DVD], 2012 April 2
  - Marion & Nell Money [3 tapes], 1984 September 14
  - George Newman [DVD], 2012 March 27
  - Donald Opstad [4 tapes], Undated
  - Marion Reid [4 tapes], 1986 July 31
  - Marion Reid [2 tapes], 1986 August 13
  - Harold Shaw, Undated
  - Ginny Sinclair, 2012 February 27
  - Donald Stewart, Undated
  - Hazel Thompson (typed recollections), 1992
  - Alice & Fred Utterback, 1985 June 4
  - B.H. "Buck" Weaver, 1983 December 1
  - Naomi Whetzel [2 tapes], Undated
  - "A Sense of Place" by Marian Winston Reid (2004) and "Life in Great Falls in the Old Days" by Beanie Lambert and Gerry Schmitz (2010) [DVD], 2011
- Series 8: Photographic Materials, c.1960s -2001
  - Sub-series 8-1: Slides, 1978-1997
    - Bradford's Barn, Georgetown Pike and Walker Road, 1994
    - Bradford House, Georgetown Pike and Walker Road, Undated
    - Coate's Garage, Georgetown Pike and Walker Road, Undated
    - Sander's House, Georgetown Pike and Walker Road, Shell Station Site, Undated
    - Oliver/Ball Store, Georgetown Pike and Walker Road, Undated
    - Town of Great Falls, Undated
    - Oliver's House, now Oliver Corner Ctr., Undated
    - Oliver's Barns, Georgetown Pike, Undated
    - Oliver's Barns, Undated
    - Diggs Farm, Undated
    - Sidney Follin Farm, Undated
    - Sidney Follin House, now Hickory Vale, Undated
    - Sidney Follin Farm, Undated
    - Sidney Follin House after renovation, Undated
    - Sidney Follin Barn now $1 million house, Undated
    - House that was Follin's Barn, 1997
    - Pearson Babson House, Undated
    - Presgrave and Miller Dairy Farm, Babson Farm, now Forestville Meadows, Undated
    - O.K. Miller's Farm at Georgetown Pike and Springvale, now Fox Vale Farm, Undated
    - Fox Vale Farm, 1978
    - Springvale Farm, Frost House, Lacy McCutchan, Undated
    - Mark Turner House, Undated
    - Turner's Barn, Undated
    - Mark Turner, Undated
    - Grace Turner, Undated
    - Mark Turner, Sr., Undated
    - Aerial view of Mark Turner Farm, Undated
    - Aerial view of Mark Turner Farm, Undated
    - Spingvale Post Office and Store, 1978
    - Daniel Bordon, Springvale Post Office Postmaster, Undated
    - Turner's Farm, Undated
    - Turner's Farm, Undated
    - S. Francis Episcopal Church, formerly Turner's Farm, Undated
    - Delk Dairy Farm c. 1920s, Old Cornwell Farm, Undated
    - Cornwell Farm back, Undated
    - Cornwell Farm (group photo), Undated
    - Wheeler Farm, Undated
    - Dr. Alfred Leigh House and Farm, Undated
    - Alfred Leigh Farm, Undated
    - Alfred Leigh Water Tower and Garage, Undated
    - Alfred Leigh Barn and Silo, Undated
    - Leigh House and Leigh Corner Shopping Center, 1997
    - Nall's Farm, Undated
    - Nall's House, 1988
    - Nall's Barn and Silo, 1988
    - Nall's Farm, 1988
    - Nall's Farm, The Ridings, Undated
    - Jesse Smith Farm, Undated
    - Smith Chapel, Undated
    - Forney type engine, Undated
    - Train at Great Falls Station, Undated
    - Great Falls and Old Dominion Bridge on Old Dominion Drive, Undated
    - Rosslyn Train Station, Undated
    - O.V. Carper's House, Undated
    - Great Falls Grange, 1980
    - Dedication of Great Falls Grange c. 1929?, Undated
    - Great Falls Grange members, Undated
    - Great Falls Grange members, Undated
    - Great Falls Grange members, Undated
    - Great Falls Grange members, Undated
    - Great Falls Grange members on Queen Mary (ship), Undated
    - Forestville School #2 1923, Undated
    - Forestville School #1 1920, Undated
    - Mr. and Mrs. Henry Cornwell and granddaughter Blanche, Undated
    - Back of Forestville School #2, Undated
    - Forestville School #2, Undated
    - Forestville School 1920, Undated
    - Forestville School #1 as bank and post office, Undated
    - Forestville School #2, Undated
    - Forestville School #1 as Library, Undated
    - Forestville School #1 as Vienna Trust & Co. Bank, Undated
    - Fire prevention program at Forestville School #3, now Great Falls School, Undated
    - Forestville School #1, Undated
    - Forestville School #2, Undated
    - Forestville School 1923, Undated
    - Forestville School 1924, Undated
    - Old Floris School, Undated
    - Andrew Chapel School, Undated
    - Henry Cornwell's House, Undated
    - Jefferson School, Undated
    - Riverbend School, Undated
    - Colvin Run School, Undated
    - Colvin Run School, Undated
    - Report card from Jefferson School, Undated
  - Sub-series 8-2: Negatives, c.1960s-2001
    - Thomas Peacock House, Undated
    - Alfred Leigh House and Joan Victor at GFHS program, Undated
    - Cornwell Mill, Undated
    - Great Falls Grange, Undated
    - "Cedars Luncheon", Undated
    - People - Misc. - Herb Sorrells, Undated
    - People - Misc. - Barbara S., Undated
    - People - Misc. - Herbert Sorrells, Buck Werner, Frank ? or Walter ?, Undated
    - People - Misc. - B.H. Werner, Undated
    - People - Misc. - Herndon Hardware Fire, Undated
    - People - Misc. - Mack and Mertyl Crippen, Undated
    - People - Misc. - John Buckner, Undated
    - Mrs. Breeden's Pictures, Undated
    - Buck's Store, Mrs. Breedon's House and Fling's House, Undated
    - Old Dominion Bridge and Misc., Undated
    - Shady Oak Store, Hick Walker, Undated
    - Turner Picture Negatives, Undated
    - Toll Gate Sign, Undated
    - 1st GFHS Festival, April 15-17, 1983, 1983 April
    - Great Falls Festival 1984, 1984
    - Great Falls Festival 1985, 1985
    - Riverboat Pilot's License, Willie Breeden, Undated
    - Ruins of Cornwell Mill / Cornwell Farm, Undated
    - Great Falls Park, Undated
    - 200th Birthday of Constitution Celebration, 1987 September 16
    - Cornwell Farm, Undated
    - Buck's Store, Undated
    - David Goldstein's House Fire, Brown House and Little Stone House, Gouldman's Farm, Undated
    - Christmas Minstrels at Safeway, 1979; Florence Murray's Fashion Show Methodist Church, Jan 1980; New Difficult Run Bridge, 1979, 1979-1980
    - Jessie Smith Farm, Ball's Store (Route 193 and Walker Road), Dickey's Tavern, Undated
    - Program at Great Falls Center, Undated
    - Elizabeth Wellman, Undated
    - Farm on Hunter Mill, Potowmac Canal, Undated
    - Shrimp Feast at Firehouse, Undated
    - Jackson Pictures, Undated
    - Bessie Van Patton Brown's Family, Undated
    - Civil War, Undated
    - Buck Werner's Retirement Party, Undated
    - 1979 Tornado, 1979
    - Bill and Catherine Campbell's 40th Anniversary Party, Undated
    - Cedar's Luncheon Party, Undated
    - Elliott Richardson School, 1993
    - Mrs. Breeden's Pictures, Undated
    - Great Falls Day 1999 (Photos by N. Whetzel), 1999 May
    - BPA Parade, 1988
    - BPA Parade Village Center, 1998?
    - Cedars, 2001 June
    - Negatives of photos from Bessie Van Patton Brown, Undated
    - Dr. Lazaro's Christmas Breakfast, Follin's Barn House, 198? December
    - Old School as bank and post office (photos by N. Whetzel), Undated
    - Back of Leigh House, Ann Cornwell Starke, Undated
    - Bill Campbell's Garage, Undated
    - Colvin Run Miller's House, Undated
    - Muriel's Father, Monahan, Undated
    - Cornwell Farm, Undated